Oh wrap yeah this one goes out to the
best TV show out there Sonic around
haters gonna hate cuz sock Underground's
gray it stop ray it's it stop ray it's
rated eight out of eight it's really
cool you love it - I know you do cuz
it's really cool Manic is green Sonia is
pink sock has a big bone what you gonna
do bout will be love Sonic sock loves
ball will be I love soccer run and it
loves me if you look down the show you
just hope you're not welcome here so get
out of here
meanwhile always if you go sweet sock
Iron Mountain's and begin to cheer [ __ ]
yeah [ __ ] yeah my ever-growing love for
this show could not be bigger
sorry man yeah if you like them to the
new my [ __ ] [ __ ] something Martin
talking all that crap this is my sock
Underground rap
[Music]